*   Home
*   Ecards
*   Photocards
*   Connect
*   Studio
*   Mobile App

*   Birthday
*   Thank You
*   Anniversary
*   Everyday
*   Love
*   Inspirational
*   Congrats
*   Friendship
*   Family
*   Cute
*   Events &. Holidays
*   MorePetsWorld LanguagesFlowersAt WorkWeddingKeep in TouchInvitations

*   Share a Smile Day
*   I Want You to be Happy Day
*   Chocolate Cheesecake Day
*   More...
    *   Daylight Saving Time Begins (Mar 8, 2020)
    *   International Women's Day (Mar 8, 2020)
    *   St. David's Day (Mar 1, 2020)
    *   Pig Day (Mar 1, 2020)
    *   Optimism Month (March 2020)
    *   American Red Cross Month (March 2020)
    *   National Anthem Day (Mar 3, 2020)
    *   Say Hi to Mom Day (Mar 5, 2020)
    *   Dentists' Day (Mar 6, 2020)
    *   Employee Appreciation Day (Mar 6, 2020)
    *   World Day of Prayer (Mar 6, 2020)
    *   Bubble Week (Mar 8 - 14, 2020)
    *   Full Moon Day (Mar 9, 2020)
    *   See All Events
*   Go

*   123Greetings»
*   Privacy Policy

*   Terms of Use
*   Privacy Policy
*   Cookie Policy
*   Copyright/IP Policy
*   Help/FAQ
*   Contact Us

Privacy Policy

**Overview** The use of the 123Greetings website(s) and/or 123Greetings software and any 123Greetings services and products (collectively, the "Website") provided by 123Greetings ("123Greetings") are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the 123Greetings Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

**General** 123Greetings takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information.

BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. 123Greetings reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms.

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Website, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the 123Greetings website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

**What information do we collect?**

**Personally Identifiable Information.** Use of certain features of the Website may require submission of certain personal information, including your and recipient’s first and last name, email address.. Account related information like name, email address, userid, date of birth, password, IP and details about your transactions that you carry related to your account, is collected in association with your use of our services. Other account related information which you may or may not provide includes mobile number, location, religion, language country, about yourself, family details and other information which may be used to provide you related content.

**Non-personally identifiable Information.** 123Greetings may also collect or receive additional non-personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Website, and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on the Website.  
  
123Greetings may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the Website and pages are visited or when a 123Greetings client is used. If we combine demographic or similar information with the Personal Information we collect, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

**Supplemented Data** Supplemented data may be received about you from other sources, including social media sites like Facebook, Twitter etc. in which case we combine this data with information that we already have about you, so that we can update, expand and analyze the accuracy of our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.

**Information you provide about third parties** The Website may permit you to provide Personal Information about third parties, such as mailing address, email addresses, or significant dates (such as birthdays or anniversaries), and may permit you to do so through the use of Social Features or a Contact Importer. If you use the website to send an ecard or any other content, we collect certain Personal Information about the recipient (such as name and email address, as applicable). We may share the information regarding your transaction with third parties as necessary to process your transaction (i.e., to create, send or deliver the card). If you choose to provide Personal Information about third parties, we will store that information only in connection with your relationship with us (e.g., to send greeting cards).

**Information third parties provide about you** We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from 123Greetings, the other website will forward your contact and other information to us so that we may contact you as requested. Further, we may receive certain information about you from third parties if you engage the third parties in connection with our Platforms – for example, if you download one of our Apps from an app store, make an in-app purchase, connect via Social Features, or make a payment using a third-party payment provider like PayPal, consistent with the privacy policies of the applicable third parties.  
  
We also may supplement the information we collect with outside records from third parties in order to provide you with information, services or goods you have requested, to enhance our ability to serve you, and to tailor our content to you. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Platforms. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Notice to the combined information.

**Cookies** 123Greetings may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Website, including to operate and improve offerings through the Website. to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Website. to remember your preferences and registration information. to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon). and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you.  
**Read our Cookie Policy:**

**Website analytics.** We use multiple web analytics tools provided by service partners such as Google Analytics, App Radar to collect information about how you interact with our website or mobile applications, including what pages you visit, what site you visited prior to visiting our website, how much time you spend on each page, what operating system and web browser you use and network and IP information. We use the information provided by these tools to improve our Services. These tools place persistent cookies in your browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone other than the service provider (ex: Google for Google Analytics). The information collected from the cookie may be transmitted to and stored by these service partners on servers in a country other than the country in which you reside. Though information collected does not include personal data such as name, address, billing information, etc., the information collected is used and shared by these service providers in accordance with their individual privacy policies.

**How we secure, store and retain your data.** We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate.  
  
We retain personal data only for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods:

*   mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations;
*   for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights. or
*   needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.

If you have any questions about the security or retention of your personal data, you can contact us at privacy@123greetings-inc.com.

**How is the information being used?** The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by 123Greetings, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you. to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services. to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries. to conduct research about your use of the Website. and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest, including but not limited to ecard sending and receiving.

Please note that 123Greetings may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while 123Greetings's business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about 123Greetings users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures, as determined by 123Greetings in good faith. Furthermore, 123Greetings may transfer personally identifiable information in the event of a transfer of ownership of 123Greetings or any of its websites or products, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy.

If you contact us for customer support regarding the website, we will not use the information you provide to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request unless you agree otherwise.

**Transfer of personal data abroad** If you utilize our Services from a country other than the country where our servers are located, your communications with us may result in transferring your personal data across international borders. Also, when you call us or initiate a chat, we may provide you with support from one of our global locations outside your country of origin. In these cases, your personal data is handled according to this Privacy Policy.

**Contests, sweepstakes and promotions** We may sponsor contests, sweepstakes or other promotions (any, a "Promotion, and collectively, "Promotions"). If you choose to participate in a Promotion, you may be required to provide certain Personal Information. By participating in a Promotion, you agree to the official rules that govern that Promotion. The official rules may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list.

**Administrative and legal reasons** We may disclose your information, including Personal Information and Usage Information, to third parties (i) if we are required to respond to subpoenas or other legal process or if in our opinion such disclosure is required by law. (ii) at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation. (iii) to protect and/or defend the website or any of the 123Greetings Companies' rights and property, or to enforce the Terms of Service or other policies applicable to the website. or (iv) to respond to an emergency or otherwise protect the personal safety, rights, property or security of any of the 123Greetings Companies or any third party. We may also use Device Identifiers, including IP addresses, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers, or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. These transfers and disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

**What is 123Greetings.com's practice regarding IP addresses?** We collect and analyze traffic on our website by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

123Greetings.com includes the sender's IP Address in the source of each ecard HTML that is created at the website. This is available to the ecard recipient and anyone else who has access to the recipient's ecard. This limits your ability to communicate anonymously using ecards. Ecards are not intended for anonymous communications, and such activity is expressly prohibited by our Terms of Use.

**What does 123Greetings.com do with the ecard messages &. information?** When you send one of our ecards, the information you provide to us is used to customize your greeting with the recipient's name and with your message, and to deliver an e-mail to the recipient. We treat our ecards as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and the contents will not be disclosed to anyone other than the intended recipient.

Under normal circumstances, we will not monitor or edit the contents of the online ecards you send. Occasion, however, we may need to view your message in connection with the technical processing of your ecard or the maintenance of our network. Also, if you ask one of our customer service representatives to help you send an ecard or to verify that an ecard was sent, that representative will be able to access all information about the ecard, including the recipient's e-mail address and the message.

If we have reason to believe, that an ecard has been sent using a false e-mail address or attempt to pose as someone else sending an ecard, information about you - including your computer's IP address - may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions.

**Third Party Ad Advertising** 123Greetings or its advertisers may use third party ad networks and ad serving companies to help sell and present advertisements online in connection with the Website. These third party ad companies may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness and to compile anonymous statistics about 123Greetings users. The use of these technologies by these third party ad companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not 123Greetings's. These third party ad companies may also monitor 123Greetings for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, "click-throughs" and/or other activities.

123Greetings does not provide advertisers access to any personally identifiable information that you have provided to 123Greetings (keeping in mind that anything you have elected to share publicly on the site is available to everyone to see).

123Greetings does not control the information collection, use, or sharing practices of third party analytics providers or advertisers. Some of these parties may collect your Personal Information when you access the Platforms or other online websites and services.

While we may use a variety of service providers to perform advertising and analytics services, some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit or https://www.aboutads.info/choices/, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program.

**Social &. interactive features. Public information** The website may provide you the opportunity to interact between the website and a third party website (such as social media platforms) and post content publicly through interactive features and through other communication functionality ("Community Forums"). You may choose, through such features or otherwise, to submit or post photographs (which may include metadata), videos, questions, comments, suggestions or other content (collectively, "User Content"). Please note that certain information, such as your name and other Personal Information, may be publicly displayed on the Platforms along with your User Content.

Anything you post to a Community Forum is public -- others will have access to your User Content and may use it or share it with third parties. Information or other content you choose to post or make available in the Community Forums may be viewed, collected and used by others. If you choose to voluntarily disclose Personal Information, that information will be considered public information and this Privacy Notice will not apply to such information. If you submit User Content, it may be published online or offline at any time. In addition, we may use your User Content and any excerpt from your User Content in connection with our advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities.

We may receive information about you from third party providers of Social Features that interact with our website. For example, if you choose to use Social Features, you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Personal Information, related to your use of the third party website or interactive service. The third party website or interactive service may allow you to remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or service, but we may retain the information previously collected in accordance with respective third-party privacy policies. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website, feature or application give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your posts, your "connections" web page, profile page, or similar page on a third party social media website, feature or application. The information we collect in connection with Social Features is subject to this Privacy Notice. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party's privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third party website or service.

**Import Contacts** The website may also allow you to import information about yourself or third parties from a third-party website or interactive service. For example, the website may allow you to provide your login information to your email account to enable the website to import your contacts or list of persons with whom you have communicated. By providing the login information in your account in any such situation, you are consenting to 123Greetings, or a party on behalf of 123Greetings, importing your contacts or list of persons with whom you have communicated for using with the website. Unless you consent, we will not store the password you provide if you import your contacts from a third party source.

**Your Control over Your Information** 123Greetings may provide functionality on some Platforms to update your contact information and/or preferences through a "My Account" (or similar) section. If you submit a request to update your contact information, 123Greetings will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Note, however, that information may persist internally for 123Greetings’ administrative purposes and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Please also note that if you are the user of one of our Apps, you may be able to review and update your Personal Information or preferences only through the website associated with that App.

You may opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from us by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those e-mails. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your use of the website and these transactional messages may be unaffected if you opt-out from marketing communications.

To opt-out of receiving direct mail, you may contact us through Customer Support at support@123greetings.com.  
Note: Because mailings often are prepared well in advance you may, for a period of time, continue to receive some offers after you send us your request.

**Data Security** 123Greetings has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personally identifiable information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our personnel that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information, are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information.

123Greetings's Privacy Policy is to share personal information only with the owner's informed consent. With your consent, from time-to-time, 123Greetings may provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know. If you have further inquires regarding 123Greetings's information sharing practices, please let us know. The designated contact for these queries is Privacy Agent, privacy@123greetings-inc.com.

**Questions and Comments** If you have any questions, comments or suggestions regarding our website's privacy policy, or regarding any other aspects of our website, please write to us.

You can also post your views to our office at:  
123Greetings.com, Inc.  
255 Executive Drive, Suite 400,  
Plainview, New York NY-11803;

**Special Note for Parents** Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, 123Greetings does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If 123Greetings learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Website without verified parental consent, then 123Greetings will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information**  
**Deletion (Opt-Out):** In order to delete the personally identifiable information you submitted, notify us at support@123greetings.com that you wish to delete your personally identifiable information or any part thereof contained at our databases.

If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.

**Modification:** If you wish to modify or update your personally identifiable information, use the Website or application interface. To easily access, view, update your personal data (where available), or to update your subscription preferences, please sign into your Account and visit "Account Settings".

If you need help, please contact us at support@123greetings.com

Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from 123Greetings's database will not prevent 123Greetings from using gathered anonymous information.

Third Parties' Practices: This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other providers of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that 123Greetings does not own or control, or does not employ or manage.

**Non-U.S. Users:** The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Website from a jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**Last Updated: May 22, 2018**

Stay Connected B'day Reminders Event Reminders Newsletter Editor Bob's Blog Site Map | Connect | Studio | Mobile App | Press Room | Blog | Widgets | RSS Feed | Recommend Us  
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy | Copyright/IP Policy | Help | Contact Us  
Copyright © 123Greetings.com, Inc.   All rights reserved.

This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse 123Greetings website, you accept the use of cookies by us and our partners.

Ok
